const STORE = [
    {
      question: 'In 2010, Lady Gaga famously wore an outlandish dress to the MTV Video Music Awards made entirely of: ____ ',
      answers: [
        'Telephones',
        'Little Kermit the Frog dolls',
        'Raw meat',
        'Condoms'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Raw meat',
    },
    {
      question: 'The iconic and spooky `Bad Romance` is from which album?',
      answers: [
        'The Fame Monster',
        'Joanne',
        'Artpop',
        'Born This Way'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'The Fame Monster',
        
    },
    {
      question: 'Let\'s take this one way back. What was Lady Gaga\'s breakout single?',
      answers: [
        'Poker Face',
        'Just Dance',
        'Paparazzi',
        'Born This Way'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Just Dance',
    },    
    {
      question: 'Finish the lyric: `Can`t read my, Can`t read my, No he can`t read my ________________',
      answers: [
        'Telephone',
        'Paparazzi',
        'Poker Face',
        'LoveGame'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Poker Face',
      
    },
    {
      question: 'What star-studded music video featured Lady Gaga posting bail thanks to another fellow Diva?',
      answers: [
        'The Edge of Glory',
        'Telephone',
        'John Wayne',
        'Judas'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Telephone',
      
    },

    {
        question: 'Who was the Diva in the previous question?',
        answers: [
            'Katy Perry',
            'Beyonce',
            'Tony Bennett',
            'Madonna'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Beyonce',
    },

    {
      question: 'Which of these album covers features Lady Gaga as a human-motorcycle hybrid?',
      answers: [
        'A Star Is Born',
        'The Fame',
        'Artpop',
        'Born This Way'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Born This Way',
    },

    {
      question: 'These questions are too easy.. Finish the lyric: `I don`t speak German, _________`',
      answers: [
      'But I do speak Italian',
      'But I can if you`d like',
      '`Cause Baby, I was Born This Way',
      'Because I`m a Gypsy'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'But I can if you`d like',
    },
  
    {
      question: 'What is Lady Gaga`s nationality?',
      answers: [
      'Italian',
      'German',
      'Swedish',
      'Romanian'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Italian',
      
    },
    {
      question: 'This one is a hard one: Where can you currently catch her live on stage?',
      answers: [
        'A town near you?',
        'Nowhere',
        'New York',
        'Las Vegas'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Las Vegas',
    
    }
];
